<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-06-16T08:49:20-05:00</updated><id>https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/feed.xml</id><title type="html">APCSA</title><subtitle>AP Computer Science A</subtitle><entry><title type="html">TT 1.0.1 Roles, Issues, and Scrum Board</title><link href="https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/techtalk/2022/06/16/TT101-roles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TT 1.0.1 Roles, Issues, and Scrum Board" /><published>2022-06-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-06-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/techtalk/2022/06/16/TT101-roles</id><author><name></name></author><category term="techtalk" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roles Scrum Master DevOps Frontend Developer Backend Developer]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TT 1.0.0 - Tools and Equipment</title><link href="https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/techtalk/2022/06/16/TT100-tools.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TT 1.0.0 - Tools and Equipment" /><published>2022-06-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-06-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/techtalk/2022/06/16/TT100-tools</id><author><name></name></author><category term="techtalk" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Equipment, accounts and tools A laptop, that you bring to class every day with the Development Tools installed on it. GitHub Account, VS Code will be used to push/pull changes. GitHub is where we store and share code in the cloud, think of Google Docs but for Code. GitHub Pages will be used to host your personal web site, notes, and experiences. Jupyter Notebooks will be used in conjunction with GitHub Pages to build running Java Code in your Technical Notes. Slack Account, install App on Laptop, get used to reading announcements. Slack is the tool will use for messaging, we have been averaging 35,000 message per class. Java is the key language you will be using in this class. Spring, Thymeleaf, HTML, CSS, JavaScript are the key supporting technicals you will be using to enhance your learning of Java. VS Code is the code editor we will be using in this class. VS Code is more than and editor, it is called and Interactive Development Environment (IDE). AWS Account for deployment, this will be provided by Teacher. AWS Cloud Commputing and Servers will be used to Deploy and Support projects.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Innovation Sprint - Technologies in Java Web Apps</title><link href="https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/tri1/2022/06/15/Tri1-innovation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Innovation Sprint - Technologies in Java Web Apps" /><published>2022-06-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/tri1/2022/06/15/Tri1-innovation</id><author><name></name></author><category term="tri1" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovation Sprint (Weeks 1 and 2) Innovation is a time to explore, learn, and obtain skills needed to reach goals. Exploration in building 1st Java Spring Web App Capturing notes while building Fastpages/GitHub pages yearlong individual notebook Reviewing the Anatomy of Java; coding using Java Primitives, Establish positve PBL hablits: a focused mindset in the classroom, using work habits to achieve success.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Overview Sprint - Java, PBL, and Tools</title><link href="https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/tri1/2022/06/15/Tri1-introduction.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Overview Sprint - Java, PBL, and Tools" /><published>2022-06-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/tri1/2022/06/15/Tri1-introduction</id><author><name></name></author><category term="tri1" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[AP CSA COURSE OUTLINE Methodology. Project Based Learning (PBL) Guideline. The 10 Units of AP Computer Science A Key Learnings for 2022-2023 Collaboratively Build, Deploy and Host Web Pages Programming, Algorithms, Databases, and APIs Team and Individual Project will highlight all 10 units, either academically or in interest fashion Establish “Real World” Scrum Team projects Preference is to establish projects with a Customer/Sponsor Projects will be tracked using GitHub README (Time Box), Issues and Projects tools Create “GitHub Pages” Individual postings and notebooks Build individual GitHub Pages Web Site to _post Notes and Learnings AP testing in May]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tri2 Overview - 2021-2022 Winter review</title><link href="https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/tri2/2022/06/15/Tri2-overview.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tri2 Overview - 2021-2022 Winter review" /><published>2022-06-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://nighthawkcoders.github.io/APCSA/tri2/2022/06/15/Tri2-overview</id><author><name></name></author><category term="tri2" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time Box Tri 2]]></summary></entry></feed>